早啊，朋友们
Good morning, guys
额..莉莉状态一直不好，但
Uh, Lele hasn't been feeling so well, but
我想她今天会好起来的，那我们来叫醒她。
I think she'll be better today. So let's wake her up.
宝贝，早安
Good morning, baby
感觉咋样？
How are you?
对不起，我只是怀孕了
Sorry, I'm just feeling pregnant
没关系，宝贝
It's okay, baby (gasp)
有东西，有东西粘上你...（啪）
You have something, you have something on your..PA
闭上眼睛，闭上眼睛
Close your eyes, close your eyes
好的，好的，好的，好的，好的
Ok, ok, ok, ok, ok
喔，我好激动
Oof, I'm excited
然后...打开！
And... open!
为啥是粉红色的？
Why is it pink?
因为我们将要有一个闺女了
Because we're gonna have a girl
现在还不知道呢
We don't know that
你好啊，塞诺拉
Excuse me, señora
等等，她是谁？
Wait, w-who's that?
她是婴儿保姆
Thats the baby's-babysitter
介绍一下，塞诺拉
Excuse me, señora
婴儿还没出生呢
The baby's not even here yet
他谁啊，塞诺拉
Excuse me, señora
等一下，等一下
One second, one second
要不-要不我们换个房间
Maybe-maybe we just go into the other room
嘘...！
Shhhhhhhhhhhh!
他可真是又瘦又弱，我都比他强
Este flacucho, se me hace que soy más fuerte que él
她说的啥？
What does that mean?
她喜欢你，不管怎样...
She loves you, anyways...
我需要收据（我要退货）
I need the receipts for this
没有
No
你俩好烦，塞诺拉
Excuse me, señora
我们可以单独聊聊吗？没有孔苏埃洛
Can we maybe speak privately, without Consuelos?
孔苏埃洛现在是一家人了，懂吗？
Consuelos is part of the family right now, ok?
好的，我们要邀请斯特罗德（摄像小哥）参加性别揭晓派对
Ok, so we're gonna invite Strode to the gender-reveal party
开始做吧！走起，准备！
Let's do it! Ok, ok ready?
给他一个惊喜，给他一个惊喜
Surprise, surprise
准备好了？
Ok, ready?
您被邀请参加-
You're invited to the-
你打扰到我了，塞诺拉
Excuse me, señora
好吧，我们给他们一些空间
Ok, well let's give them some space
！空间？！不，不，不，这是我的房子！
¡Que?! Space?! No no no no this is my house!
他俩从不干活，啥都不做！
they're never working, they‘re never do anything!
道歉，对不起
So sorry, so sorry
这是一个-
This is a-
好了，走吧！好了，走吧！赶快！
Ok, lets go! Ok, lets go! Hurry up!
我们走！
Lets go!
喔！
Woo!
嘿！
Ey!
我们不确定他是个女孩。不能确定
We have no idea its a girl. No idea
他就是个女孩
It is a girl
我好像知道，应该就是个女孩！
Like, I know its going to be a girl!
我都不用看结果（就是女孩），我-
I don't even know, I-I-
特万！特万！我知道他挺激动的-特万，
Twan! Twan! I know he's pretty exited-Twan,
来这里，见见闺蜜们，特万！
come here, meet the girls, meet the girls Twa-TWAN!
亲亲！哦，我的天哪，斯特罗德，斯特罗德，斯特罗德，听着，
Kisses! Oh my god, Strode, Strode, Strode look,
听着，孔苏埃洛，孔苏埃洛有话要告诉你
look, Consuelo, Consuelo has something to tell
这是阿莫尔，我儿子，现在也是你儿子
Amor, this is my son, now your son
爸爸！！
Papa!!
斯特罗德？斯特罗德？
Strode? Strode?
嘿，不对吗？
Hey, uh, no?
爸爸！爸爸！爸爸！
¡Papa! ¡Papa! ¡Papa!
别跑啊！
No!
斯特罗德，是你的家人！
Strode, it's your family!
是你的家人呐，斯特罗德！
It's your family, Strode!
好吧，斯特罗德跑了，现在我得自己摄像
Ok, so Strode left and now I'm taking care of the camera now
亲爱的！
Sweetie!
我很讨厌现在的生活，亲们
I hate my life so much, guys
什么？
What?
不，宝贝。我爱现在的生活，是吧？亲们
No, babe. I love my life, right? guys
当然，必须，是啊，
Yeah! Yeah, yeah
干杯！到永远！！？
Cheers! To ever, right?
好
Ok
哟，您男友在给你穿小鞋呢
Yo, you got a boyfriend or shomething
什么？
What?
特万！
Twan!
TWAN!
干啥？！我啥也没做！
What?! I'm not doing nothing!
我马上回来！
I'll be right back!
斯特罗德？！
Strode?!
斯特罗德！
Strode!
斯特罗
Stro-
斯特罗德，从那里下来！
Strode get down from there!
不！
No!
快下来！快下来！！不然-
Get down-get-get down before!-
别让我-别让我
Don't make me-don't make me
来了
Ay
大家好，这位是万医生，他来公布性别
Hey guys, so this is Dr. Wan and he's has the gender review
好的，大家都倒计时了吗？
Ok, everybody for a little countdown?
开始吧！
Let's do it!
3 2 1
3, 2, 1
是个男孩！我们要有一个儿子了！
We're having a boy! We're having a boy!
我们要有一个儿子了！
WE'RE HAVING A BOY!
耶，我还有一件事要宣布...
Yeah, and I got one more thing to tell ya...
呃，你怀了双胞胎
Uh, you're having twins
有一个是闺女吗？
Is one of them a girl?!
不，也是儿子
No, its a boy...
俩儿子！俩儿子！有俩儿子！
BOYS! BOYS! WERE HAVING BOYS!
俩儿子，朋友们！
2 boys everyone!
你造吗？！我要跟你和孩子们分开一阵儿！
You know what?! I'm going to take a break from you and the kids!
你不能这样做！
You cannot do that!
为什么不？！
Why not?!
因为他们在你肚子里！
Because they're in your stomach!
那好，那我要和你分手！
Ok, well I'm breaking up with you!
不行，你不能和我分手！
No n-listen you cannot break up with me!
为什么？！？！？！？！？！？
WHY?!?!?!?!?!?
因为我要娶你
Because im marring you
嫁给我吧...
Please...